<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tru2Specs</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- login strings-->
    <string name="login_email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="login_forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="login_sign_in_option_msg">Sign in using social network</string>
    <string name="login_sign_in_option_msg_or">OR</string>
    <string name="login_fb">{fa-facebook}</string>
    <string name="login_gplus">{fa-google-plus}</string>
    <string name="login_not_a_member_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login_not_a_member_sign_in">Sign In</string>

    <!--sign up strings -->
    <string name="signup_firstname">Full Name</string>
    <string name="signup_lastname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="signup_re_password">Retype Password</string>
    <string name="signup_dob">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="signup_calendar">{fa-calendar}</string>
    <string name="signup_select_gender">select your gender</string>
    <string name="signup_agree_terms">i agree the terms of use</string>
    <string name="signup_sign_up">sign up</string>
    <string name="signup_already_a_member_sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="reset_password_text">Enter your registered email id and we will email you a link to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="reset_password_btn_text">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="dummy_amount">\u20B9120</string>
    <string name="rupees">\u20B9</string>
    <string name="address_save_and_continue">Save and continue</string>
    <string name="address_select_from_saved">Saved addresses</string>
    <string name="adress_address_line_1">Address Line 1</string>
    <string name="adress_address_line_2">Address Line 2</string>
    <string name="address_city">City</string>
    <string name="address_state">State</string>
    <string name="address_zip_code">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="address_country">Country</string>
    <string name="complete_thank_you">Thank you</string>
    <string name="complete_msg">We\'ve sent you an email with all the details of your order. You can track your shipment with the order id below.</string>
    <string name="complete_back_to_shop">Back to shop</string>
    <string name="no_items_in_bag">You have no items in your shopping bag.</string>
    <string name="no_item_shop_now">Continue shopping</string>
    <string name="order_id">order id</string>
    <string name="order_amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="order_items">Items</string>
    <string name="order_placed_on">Placed on Thursday</string>
    <string name="order_in_progress">In progess</string>
    <string name="order_view_details">View detail</string>
    <string name="signup_email">Email</string>
    <string name="signup_phone">Contact No</string>
    <string name="signup_referral">Referral Code (Optional)</string>
    <string name="basic_info_contact_no">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="basic_info_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="basic_info_full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="login_google_plus">Login with Google+</string>
    <string name="login_facebook">login with facebook</string>
    <string name="login_not_a_member">Not a member?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="near_by_stores">Nearby stores</string>
    <string name="title_store">Stores</string>
    <string name="title_home">HOME</string>

    <!--facebook login related strings-->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1387032194715155</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1387032194715155</string>
    <string name="filter_sort">sort</string>
    <string name="filter">filter</string>
    <string name="dashboard_my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="dashboard_my_orders">My Orders</string>
    <string name="google_client_id">857287145083-2tl4c9tq347m2r7vt6qjk5lmt4fq020q.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="dashboard_serviecs_store_locator">Store\nLocator</string>
    <string name="dashboard_serviecs_home_checkup">Home eye\ncheckup</string>
    <string name="dashboard_serviecs_try_at_home">Try at home\nfor free</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="action_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="action_account">Account</string>
    <string name="login_already_a_member">Already a member?</string>
    <string name="action_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="title_sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="profile_update">Update</string>
    <string name="profile_add_new_address">Add a new address</string>
    <string name="title_my_accout">My Account</string>
    <string name="title_add_address">Add Address</string>
    <string name="address_lankdmark">Landmark</string>
    <string name="address_mobile">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="address_alt_mobile">Alternate Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="adress_default">Make this my default address</string>
    <string name="saved_addresses">Saved Addresses</string>
    <string name="title_cart">Shopping Bag</string>
    <string name="cart_checkout">Proceed to checkout</string>
    <string name="title_price_details">price details</string>
    <string name="title_price">Price (2 items)</string>
    <string name="title_delivery">Delivery</string>
    <string name="title_amount_payable">Amount Payable</string>
    <string name="title_checkout">Delivery</string>
    <string name="title_product_details">PRODUCT NAME &amp; CODE</string>
    <string name="checkout_address">Address</string>
    <string name="text_save_and_continue">Save and continue</string>
    <string name="checkout_card_details">Card details</string>
    <string name="checkout_pay_now">pay now</string>
    <string name="checkout_enter_card_detail_msg">Enter your debit and credit card details</string>
    <string name="checkout_card_no">Card No</string>
    <string name="checkout_expiry">Expiry</string>
    <string name="checkout_card_cvv">CVV Code</string>
    <string name="find_a_store">Find a store</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="buy_now">Buy now</string>
    <string name="lbl_price">Price</string>
    <string name="remove_item">Remove</string>
    <string name="shortlist">shortlist</string>
    <string name="use_for">You use Eyeglasses for:</string>
    <string name="poid">poid</string>
    <string name="select_section">Select Section</string>
    <string name="title_favorite">Shortlisted</string>
    <string name="no_items_shortlisted">You have not shortlisted any items.</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="select_lens">Select lens</string>
    <string name="bullet">•</string>
    <string name="faqs">Faq</string>
    <string name="reset_all">Reset All</string>
    <string name="apply_filter">Apply filters</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">SECURITY AND PRIVACY
 
DealsKart Online Services Private Limited, a private limited company duly incorporated under the provisions of the Companies Act, 1956 (hereinafter referred to as ‘Company’), Company knows that You (a visitor or a registered user) care how information about You is used and shared, and we appreciate Your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We let You retain as much control as possible over Your personal information. However, You may not visit and use our site at any time without telling us who You are or revealing the required information about Yourself. To the Company, our most important asset is our relationship with You. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users of our site. We are proud of our privacy practices and the strength of our site security and want you to know how we protect Your information and use it to provide to You the services. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting this Website, You are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
 
Information You Give Us: We receive any information You enter on our Website or give us in any other way, which is stored on the Company’s secure servers. To clarify, personal information means and includes name, email, website user account log in ID and password, mobile and landline phone numbers, gender, DOB, address, gift message and eye prescription, but excludes any Credit Card, Debit Card or Net-Banking Details, all of which are stored on the Company’s secure servers and/or in cookies on your computer.
 
You can choose not to provide certain information, but then You might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that You provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future commercial transactions, and communicating with You and utilising/disclosing, without prejudice to any of Your other rights, the same for any other, whether commercial or non-commercial purpose which the Company in its sole discretion considers necessary for its business purposes or otherwise.
 
You can add or update certain information. When You update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
 
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever You interact with us. Our server logs Your activities for various diagnostic and analytical purposes. However, other than the IP address of Your machine from where You are accessing the Service, there are no other personal information maintained by the Company in the logs.
 
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may request to receive a confirmation when You open e-mail from Your end if Your computer supports such capabilities.
 
Sharing of Information Received by the Company: You can tell when another business is involved along with us in processing Your transactions, and we share, use or, disclose customer information related to processing of those transactions with that business as needed to fulfill your order
 
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might be acquired completely or merge with any other company. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In such a case, we will ensure the protection of Your information as per these policies and guidelines. You hereby specifically consent and grant permission to the disclosure, and transferring, of information to such third parties.
 
Protection of the Company and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and other similar matters. You hereby specifically consent and grant permission to disclosure and transferring of information to such third parties, as maybe required.
 
SECURITY OF INFORMATION
 
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software during the part where you enter your credit card or net banking details, which encrypts information You input. We constantly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges. We do not and will not sell or rent Your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time, unless it is in (i) in response to a valid legal request by a law enforcement officer or government agency or (ii) where You have given Your consent, or (iii) utilize the same for some statistical or other representation without disclosing personal data.
 
The information collected from You will be stored on the Company’s secured server and systems. The Company maintains secure and reasonable security practices and procedures which are proprietary and unique to the Company (“Security Practice”). Such Security Practice involves measures such as but not limited to password protection, limitation of access to specified personnel on a need to know basis, and security measures including encryption if required and other physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to the server and systems and information residing on such server and systems. The Company’s Security Practice protects against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of the information. The Company’s Security Practice contains managerial, technical, operational and physical security control measures which are commensurate with the information assets being protected and with the nature of business. You acknowledge and agree that the Security Practice and procedures as mentioned above are reasonable and are designed to protect the information provided by You.
 
We only reveal those numbers of Your account as required to enable us to access and provide You the required services relating to Your accounts.
 
We make every effort to allow You to retain the anonymity of Your personal identity and You are free to choose a Login ID email address and password that keeps Your personal identity anonymous. Access to Your Registration Information and Your personal financial data is strictly restricted to those of our Company employees and contractors, strictly on a need to know basis, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These employees or contractors may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
 
With the exception of a Login ID in the form of an email address, which may be provided on an anonymous basis, and Your Third Party Account Information, which is required for providing the services, the Company does not require any information from You that might constitute personally identifiable information.
 
It is important for You to protect against unauthorized access to Your password and to Your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
 
As described in this Agreement and with Your consent, the Company will from time to time connect electronically to Your online bank, credit card and other online financial accounts to process Your Order.
 
Company will also use other third parties like courier companies to deliver products that you order on our website, to your delivery address.
 
CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS
 
Please do read the detailed terms and conditions of the Company’s Website situated at http://www.Tru2Specs.com/terms-conditions. If You choose to visit this Website, Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Republic of India. If You have any concern about privacy at this Website, please send us a thorough description to support@Tru2Specs.com and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Website Use may also change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless You have instructed us not to, but You should check our Website frequently to see recent changes.
 
GRIEVANCE OFFICER
 
The Company would be glad to provide assistance to You in case You have any queries or have any issues pertaining to this Security and Privacy policy. Kindly contact Mr. Saurabh Asthana at saurabha@valyoo.in.
 
LIST OF COOKIES WE COLLECT
 
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
 
COOKIE name

COOKIE Description

CART

The association with your shopping cart.

CATEGORY_INFO

Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.

COMPARE

The items that you have in the Compare Products list.

CURRENCY

Your preferred currency

CUSTOMER

An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.

CUSTOMER_AUTH

An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.

CUSTOMER_INFO

An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.

CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS

Stores the Customer Segment ID

EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE

A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.

FRONTEND

You session ID on the server.

GUEST-VIEW

Allows guests to edit their orders.

LAST_CATEGORY

The last category you visited.

LAST_PRODUCT

The most recent product you have viewed.

NEWMESSAGE

Indicates whether a new message has been received.

NO_CACHE

Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.

PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART

A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.

POLL

The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.

POLLN

Information on what polls you have voted on.

RECENTLYCOMPARED

The items that you have recently compared.

STF

Information on products you have emailed to friends.

STORE

The store view or language you have selected.

USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE

Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.

VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS

The products that you have recently viewed.

WISHLIST

An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.

WISHLIST_CNT

The number of items in your Wishlist.

 
Policy for NDNC

By using the website and/or registering yourself at Tru2Specs.com you authorize us to contact you via email or phone call or sms and offer you our services, imparting product knowledge, offer promotional offers running on website &amp; offers offered by the associated third parties, for which reasons, personally identifiable information may be collected. And Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC or NCPR service, you still authorize us to give you a call from the Tru2Specs for the above mentioned purposes till 45 days of your registration with us. This Privacy Policy covers Tru2Specs’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Tru2Specs collects when you are on the Tru2Specs site, and when you use Tru2Specs’s services. This policy also covers Tru2Specs’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Tru2Specs’s business partners share with Tru2Specs. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tru2Specs does not own or control or to people that Tru2Specs does not employ or manage. Tru2Specs collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Tru2Specs account, when you use certain Tru2Specs products or services, when you visit Tru2Specs pages, and when you enter promotions. Tru2Specs may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. When you register with Tru2Specs, we ask for your first name, last name, contact no, email, Date of birth and gender. Once you register with Tru2Specs and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Also during registration, you may be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, pager, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorize us to send sms/email alerts to you for your login details and any other service requirements or some advertising messages/emails from us.

</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title"><![CDATA[Privacy & Policy]]></string>
    <string name="no_products_found">Sorry no result found!\nPlease try a different search.</string>
</resources>
